There's a difference between I can't and
I just haven't done it yet.
>> like to build my Coast Starlight
furniture using no nails. To make a
dowel, you got to get a small piece of
wood. I am using this rip off of a piece
of cedar and unadvisably cutting it like
this.
Now you know why it's called a skill
saw. Protect your hands.
If it don't measure in centimeters,
it'll break after a week here. Cut it.
You got to do the old Michael Jackson.
Just beat it.
Yeah, Jesus was a carpenter, right?
I wonder how he liked bevels.
Here's one. How many you need? At least
six per bench. I'm thinking I'm going to
come off here at a 10° bevel and then
the same thing back this way and then
one more back that way. I am a redneck
with a plan. Do you doubt me?
I got my jig cut in there. Got me a
little coupon. My lines lined up.
Hey.
Hey, it worked.
Hey, I'm telling you
two for two.
Huh, yeah, hot diggity dog. Yeah, that's
encouraging.
What are we doing?
Hm.
Are we making a bench or wasting hours
of our life?
No, it's it's pretty damn good.
Hey, I made a bench out of dowels. I've
never done that before. As you see me
sitting on the first dowel bench I've
ever built, it's a reminder everybody
can do things they've done before, but
you got to try things that you've never
done to see what you're able to do.
There's a difference between I can't and
I just haven't done it yet. Always try
things that push yourself because you'll
go places you never thought possible.
Like sitting on your ass at Coast
Starlight.